"BUT IF"
"I HAVE SOME"
"TIME"
"I MIGHT TRY"
"TO SEE YOU."
"MISS YOU VERY"
"MUCH."
COPY AND
PASTE IT
IN EVERY CHANNEL
TO EVERY B*TCH
AND THEY'LL READ
THAT SHIT
BUT THEN THEY CAN'T
GO:
"WELL YOU'RE ALWAYS"
"BUSY, YOU'RE"
"ALWAYS WITH"
"OTHER H*ES."
THEY CAN'T REPLY
TO YOU
DO YOU NOT SEE
THE BRILLIANCE?
ALL THEY CAN
DO IS READ IT,
THEN WHEN YOU
WANT TO FUCK THEM,
YOU HIT ON THE
TELEGRAM CHANNEL
"WILL BE CALLING"
"YOU IN A FEW"
"MINUTES,"
"STAY BY"
"YOUR PHONE"
UNBLOCK.
CALL.
COME HERE, LET'S
FUCK.
"ACTUALLY I'M TIRED OF"
"YOU..."
OKAY. BYE. BOOM.
TELL HER IN THE TELEGRAM
CHANNEL,
"WHEN YOU START BEHAVING"
"YOURSELF,"
"YOU CAN EMAIL"
"ME AT THIS"
"ADDRESS"
IF SHE EMAILS
YOU SAYING SORRY,
SHE GETS FUCKED
AGAIN. IF SHE
DOESN'T, MOVE
ON, BANG
BANG, EVERY
N*GGER-PIMPIN KNOW...
...B*TCHES COME AND GO.
NO BIG DEAL
YOU AIN'T GOT
TIME TO BE
WHATSAPP'ING
THESE HOES
"WHAT YOU DOING TODAY?"
"I HAVE TO"
"GO TO WORK"
"TODAY."
"OH THAT SOUNDS"
"FUN AND"
"MAH MAH MAH"
"WAH WAH WAH"
HOW THE FUCK
YOU GONNA GET RICH
IF YOU DOING THAT
SHIT
YOU AIN'T GOT TIME!